Somebody help me out!
Oh, my god!
Walt! Walt!
Stay away from the gas! Stay there!
Help! Help!
Somebody help me!
My leg!
Hey, get over here! Give me a hand!
You! Come on! Come over here! Give me a hand!
On the count of 3!
1...
2...
3!
Help!
Please! Help me! Help me! Help me!
All right, get him out of here!
Get him away from the engine!
Get him out of here!
I'm having contractions.
- How many months pregnant are you?
- I'm eight months.
And how far apart are they coming?
I don't know. I think it just happened.
Hey! Hey, hey, get away!
Listen to me.
Look at me. You're gonna be okay, do you understand me?
But you have to sit absolutely still.
Hey, you!
Come here!
I need you to get this woman away from these fumes.
Take her over there. Stay with her.
If her contractions occur any closer than three minutes apart, call out for me.
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
- I'll be  right back, okay?
- Thank you.
Hey! What's your name?!
Jack!
Stop.
Her head's not tilted far back enough.
You're blowing air into her stomach.
Are you sure?
That's exactly what I was doing.
I'm a lifeguard. I'm licensed.
Yeah, well, you need to seriously think about giving that license back.
Maybe we should do one of those hole things.
You know, stick that pen in the throat.
Yeah, good idea. You go get me a pen.
Does anyone have any pens?
Do you have a pen?
Come on.
Come on! Come on! Come on.
Big deep breaths.
Big breaths.
Move! Move! Move!
Get her out of there! The wing !
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
You?
Stay with her.
Dude, I'm not going anywhere.
I didn't know which one worked best.
They're all good.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Did you ever use a needle?
What?
Did you ever patch a pair of jeans?
I made the drapes in my apartment.
That's fantastic. Listen,
do you have a second?
I could use a little help here.
Help with what?
With this.
Look, I'd do it myself. I'm a doctor,
but I just can't reach --
- You want me to sew that up?
- It'd be just like the drapes --
No, with the drapes, it was a sewing machine.
No, you can do this. I'm telling you.
If you wouldn't mind.
- Of course I will.
- Thank you.
It's for your hands.
Save me some.
For the-- for the wound.
Any color preference?
No. Standard black.
Hey, you.
What's your name?
Me? Charlie.
Charlie.
We need help with the fire.
No one will see it if it isn't big.
Okay, I'm on it.
What's your name?
- Sayid.
- Sayid. I'm on it, Sayid.
I might throw up on you.
You're doing fine.
You don't seem afraid at all.
I don't understand that.
Well,
fear's sort of an odd thing.
When I was in residency,
my first solo procedure was a spinal surgery
on a 16-year-old kid.
A girl.
And at the end, after 13 hours,
I was closing her up, and I --
I accidentally ripped her dural sac.
Shredded the base of the spine
where all the nerves come together.
Membrane, stenos tissue.
So it ripped open.
Nerves just spilled out of her
like angel hair pasta.
Spinal fluid flowing out of her, and I --
and the terror was just so... crazy.
So real.
And I knew I had to deal with it.
So I just made a choice.
I'd let the fear in. Let it take over.
Let it do its thing.
But only for five seconds.
That's all I was gonna give it.
So I started to count.
1...
2...
3...
4...
5.
Then it was gone.
I went back to work, sewed her up,
and she was fine.
If that had been me,
I think I would have run for the door.
Well, I don't think that's true.
You're not running now.
FATE
You'd think they would have come by now.
What? Who?
Anyone.
As if I'm gonna start eating chocolate.
Shannon, we may be here for a while.
The plane had a black box, idiot.
They know exactly where we are. They're coming.
I'll eat on the rescue boat.
I'll eat on the rescue boat!
- Hungry?
- Yeah. Thanks.
Any more, uh, you know, baby stuff?
No. I'm -- I'm okay.
- Well, hang in there.
- Yeah, you too.
You sure you're warm enough?
Do you think he's gonna live?
Do you know him?
He was sitting next to me.
We must have been at about
40,000 feet when it happened.
Hit an air pocket
and dropped maybe...
200 feet.
The turbulence was...
I blacked out.
I didn't.
I saw the whole thing.
I knew that the tail was gone, but I...
couldn't bring myself to look back.
And then the --
the front end of the plane broke off.
Well, it's not here on the beach.
Neither is the tail.
We need to figure out which way we came in.
Why?
'Cause there's a chance we could find the cockpit.
If it's intact, we might be able to find the transceiver,
and we could send a signal
and help the rescue party find us.
How do you know all that?
Took a couple flying lessons.
It wasn't for me.
I saw some smoke.
Just through the valley.
If you're thinking about going for the cockpit,
I'm going with you.
I don't know your name.
- I'm Kate.
- Jack.
What was that?
That was weird, right?
Is that Vincent?
It's not Vincent.
Did anybody see that ?
Yeah.
Boone!
Terrific.
So how's the drink?
It's good.
That wasn't a very strong reaction.
Well, it's not a very strong drink.
Just don't tell anyone.
This of course breaks some
critical FAA regulations.
Excuse me.
Sir, excuse me?
I guess he really had to go.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the pilot has switched on
the "fasten seatbelts" sign.
Please return to your seats
and fasten your seatbelts.
It's normal.
Oh, I know.
I've just never been a very food flyer.
My husband keeps reminding me that planes
want to be in the air.
Well, he sounds like a very smart man.
I'll be sure and tell him that
when he gets back from the bathroom.
Well, I'll keep you company until he does.
Don't worry.
It's gonna be over.
It sounded like an animal.
That sound that it made,
I keep thinking that there was
something really familiar about it.
- Where are you from?
- The Bronx.
- Might be monkeys.
- Sure. It's monkey island...
You ready?
Kate, you showed me where the smoke was.
I can get there myself.
I'm coming.
Well, you're gonna need better shoes.
Whatever it was,
it wasn't natural.
Does anyone have any sunblock ?
Yeah, I do.
So,
I was just looking inside the fuselage.
It's pretty grim in there.
Do you think we should do
something about the, uh...
B-o-d-y-s?
What are you spelling, man, bodies?
B-o-d-I-e-S.
That sounds like a good idea.
No, they'll deal with it when they get here.
I'm gonna go out and look for the cockpit.
See if we can find a transceiver
to send a distress signal, help the rescue team.
You're gonna need to keep
an eye on the wounded.
If the guy in the suit wakes up,
try to keep him calm,
but don't let him remove that piece of shrapnel.
You understand?
Yeah. Got it. What about the guy with the leg, the tourniquet?
Stopped the bleeding. I took it off last night.
He should be all right.
Yeah. Cool. Good job.
I'll come with. I want to help.
Nah, I don't need any more help.
No, it's cool. Don't really feel
like standing still, so...
Excellent.
Can I ask you something?
Me?
I'd be thrilled.
I've been waiting.
Have we ever met anywhere?
No. That would be unlikely.
- I look familiar, though, right?
- Yeah.
- Can't quite place it?
- No, I can't.
Yeah. I think I know.
You do?
"you all, everybody
you all, everybody"
You never heard that song?
- I've heard it. I just don't know what the hell
- That's us... Driveshaft.
Look, the ring.
Second tour of Finland.
You never heard of Driveshaft?
- The band?
- Yeah, the band.
- You were in Driveshaft?
- I am. I play bass.
- Serious?
- Yeah. Charlie.
Track 3, you know, I do backing vocals.
My friend Beth would freak. She loves you guys.
Give me Beth's number. I'll call her. I'd love to.
- Hey.
- You ever heard of Driveshaft?
You all, everybody
you all, every...body
we got to keep moving.
They were good.
They are good.
Still together.
In the middle of a comeback.
Hey, guys, is this normal?
Kind of day turning into night,
you know, end of the world-type weather.
Is this -- guys?
I'm telling you, you don't wanna go in there!
There's too many bodies!
There it is again.
Oh my god.
Well, let's do this.
- Let's get this trans--
- Transceiver.
- Transceiver thing and get out of here.
Come on! Come on!
You okay?
Yeah. You?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
Charlie's fine, by the way. I'm okay.
Hey, you don't have to come up here.
No, I'm good.
So, what does a transceiver look like?
Like a complicated walkie-talkie.
Hey! Can you hear me?
I need that water.
Here. Here you go.
- How many survived?
- At least 48.
Does anything feel broken?
No, no. Just my head -- it's a little dizzy, that's all.
It's probably a concussion.
- How long has it been?
- 16 hours.
16 --
- Has anybody come?
- Not yet.
Six hours in,
our radio went out.
No one could see us.
We turned back to land in Fiji.
By the time we hit turbulence,
we were a thousand miles off course.
They're looking for us in the wrong place.
We have a transceiver.
Good. Good, that's what we were hoping.
- Listen, you shouldn't try to move.
- No, no. I'm okay.
The transceiver's right there.
It's right there.
Where's Charlie?
It's not working.
Charlie?
What were you doing in the bathroom?
What?
What the hell was that?
Kate.
It's right outside.
What? What's right outside?
What the hell just happened?!
Jack, come on!
Just leave it!
Hey !
Run!
Jack!
1...
2...
3...
4...
5.
Kate!
- Where the hell's Jack?
- I don't know!
- Did you see him?
- Yeah, he pulled me up.
- Where is he?
- I don't know!
- How can you not know?
- We got separated!
Look, I fell down. He came back for me.
That thing was --
Did you see it ?
No. No. But it was right there.
We were dead. I was, and then
Jack came back and he pulled me up.
I don't know where he is.
- We have to go back for him.
- Go back? There?
Kate, there's a certain gargantuan quality
about this thing.
Then don't come.
Kate!
I heard you shout.
I heard you shout "Jack."
I'm Charlie, by the way.
What is that?
What --
It's the pilot.
Did you see it?
No. It was right behind me,
but I dove into the bushes.
Guys?
How do something like that happen?
Subtitles by Travis and RaceMan
www.forom.com
Warning: spoilers on episode 2 are next.
There are 2 bachelors to choose from.
The season premiere of The Bachelor is next.
Mayday ! Mayday !
I've just been through a trauma here. Okay ?
We've all been through a trauma.
I haven't felt the baby move since yesterday.
Give it a break.
I know your type.
You saw what that thing did to the pilot.
What makes you think we're any safer here
than we are in the jungle ?
If you see anything, run!
What is that ?
Something else is already transmitting.
That's weird.
What is she saying ?
What is this ?
Come here!
Break it up!
Come on! Bring it!
Go on!
Stop!
Something is coming.
It's coming towards us I think.
Let it go !
Guys... where are we ?
An all new Lost.
Next Wednesday 8/7c
only on ABC.
www.tvsubtitles.net